{
  "LANGHINDI": 17,
  "qu1": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>In a classification dataset, there are 400 labeled examples belonging to 5 distinct classes. If each class has an equal number of examples, how many examples are there in each class?</p>",
      "OPT1": "80",
      "OPT2": "100",
      "OPT3": "200",
      "OPT4": "400",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu2": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following machine learning algorithm is suitable for solving regression problems?</p>",
      "OPT1": "K-Means clustering",
      "OPT2": "Random Forest",
      "OPT3": "K-Nearest Neighbors (KNN)",
      "OPT4": "Apriori algorithm",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu3": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a KNN classifier with K = 5, if the majority class among the 5 nearest neighbors is class A, what is the predicted class for a new data point?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Class A",
      "OPT2": "Class B",
      "OPT3": "Cannot be determined",
      "OPT4": "Depends on the distance metric",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu4": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn ridge regression, if the penalty parameter \u03bb is set to 0.1, what effect does it have on the regression coefficients?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Increases bias and reduces variance",
      "OPT2": "Reduces bias and increases variance",
      "OPT3": "Reduces both bias and variance",
      "OPT4": "Increases both bias and variance",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu5": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a logistic regression model, if the odds ratio for a predictor variable is 2.5, what is the estimated increase in the odds of the outcome for a one-unit increase in the predictor variable?</p>",
      "OPT1": "2.5",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "KJIJJkOnekP6fORytGMbwg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": " ",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0"
  },
  "qu6": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a simple linear regression model, if the coefficient of determination (<em>R</em><sup>2</sup>) is 0.64, what percentage of the variation in the dependent variable is explained by the independent variable (in %)?</p>",
      "OPT1": "64",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "cbJrKHkPIMoqZRj+kuE7Ow==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu7": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a naive Bayes classifier, if the probability of class A given the predictor variables is 0.7 and the probability of class B given the same predictor variables is 0.3, what is the predicted class for a new data point?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Class A",
      "OPT2": "Class B",
      "OPT3": "Cannot be determined",
      "OPT4": "Depends on the feature space",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "Dsdj/LJX8pBs6q+b96fwiQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu8": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a Linear Discriminant Analysis (LDA) model with two classes, if the Mahalanobis distance between a new data point and the mean of class A is 3 and the Mahalanobis distance between the same data point and the mean of class B is 2, what is the predicted class?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Class A",
      "OPT2": "Class B",
      "OPT3": "Depends on the prior probabilities",
      "OPT4": "Depends on the covariance matrix",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu9": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a simple linear regression model, if the slope coefficient is 0.6 and the intercept is 2, what is the predicted value of the dependent variable when the independent variable is 5?</p>",
      "OPT1": "3",
      "OPT2": "4",
      "OPT3": "5",
      "OPT4": "6",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu10": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a logistic regression model, if the odds ratio for a predictor variable is 0.4, what is the estimated decrease in the odds of the outcome for a one-unit increase in the predictor variable?</p>",
      "OPT1": "0.4",
      "OPT2": "0.6",
      "OPT3": "0.8",
      "OPT4": "1.2",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu11": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a supervised learning dataset, if there are 100 labeled examples and each example has 10 features, how many labels are there in total?</p>",
      "OPT1": "10",
      "OPT2": "100",
      "OPT3": "1000",
      "OPT4": "10000",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "1.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.33",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu12": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich evaluation metrics is commonly used for classification tasks when class imbalance is present?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Mean squared error",
      "OPT2": "Accuracy",
      "OPT3": "F1-score",
      "OPT4": "R-squared",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "9m/iwvJKC6coEJr5HJJczQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu13": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn a semi-supervised learning dataset, if there are 1000 examples and only 100 examples are labeled, what is the ratio of labeled to unlabeled examples?</p>",
      "OPT1": "0.111",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "q4H8M2BNqL8DZ5y0GU8GVQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu14": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn an unsupervised learning dataset with 500 examples and 15 features each, what is the total number of labels?</p>",
      "OPT1": "0",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "0",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu15": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tA set of observation of independent variable <img align=\"absmiddle\" alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABMAAAAgCAYAAADwvkPPAAACQElEQVRIS+2VXUiTcRTGf5OIqDH6MBgSEdEaRELsppFe7CZoELUZaZ9oKEa4YtjF8KuWX1HgNsIlVsLGqHDSnEGUEGEhKYy8MIJiIV1ESTWIMcos9/bfV22luIne+b99D8/znOc857wySTwW6cmWwXJ2ctmznC1jqTybZnLITvM7A50VavLmFDZF0GXl9pZzXNAVZNQllUWJjDkpa4CWvho08rmh4hyRAI7DNmjrwqxZ+4c2ARb/WE/IcpcWXX4WZk3zwW9hX/dWXGnkAuy7FHRVoe/djTcbVSmq8BBN2jpC7b10GjbH25VJM68lt7GEjkInw606FPHiJLPZD3o7j5wGlJ9GcDbWclN5OVn3haHGQ1S9PMXD/gpUAk0mfeyXqrXN4LjPDcOmBG94BPeAAqM2QPnexxgGm9gwOI6qooipiTwKdymFktggREfW9XSM2jioXIHs5wubpC3xoEkHS7USfYPbeJQ7GDnbZWF/wco0P38x6a+l2PwWk88rBiGfB4wIY/ZSSl9VM3xLtJoxmpzBvgqwSgF2MjuwhGcNfLb6uJcR1lj2emi7/oQHz7dzbfQiOkV6/lLK+OvZ/9MME3w2wZptIXq6v1F5egbrHg87fHb0414CRSZOqFaJhmebpvRDigewXpFglweF6SIqG+vocxxDvfo9AzVlnH+6E1P7GY4c0KCMCZw1ZwvagKjAukTxlfx/NyD2q1vAbh73sO5qK+XqRMxjL+0ELdrVyGK3syhZquOYBfU8JcvKcvfwN++hbLDJ1/QQAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC\" /> and the corresponding dependent (y) is given below:</p>\r\n<p>\r\n\t<img alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAQ8AAABCCAYAAABJnlM4AAAL2UlEQVR4Xu1dfUxV5x1+6EyzbNqaVRMRtyU2A5pgOgVJTPsHheBsKtNANyMqmEsdpLSiji8HtGtBUS6xQMXqDDeCLU4XmAUNTiLSZC6ZhUTHEoHIsuksNXVJpWTrGmU7534oH/fec87vvu8559787r/3Pe/7Ps/zO8/7cc55f1H/U37gHzPADDADBhmIYvMwyBgXZwaYATcDbB4cCMwAM0BigM2DRBtfxAwwA2weHAPMADNAYoDNg0QbX8QMMANsHhwDzAAzQGKAzYNEG1/EDDADbB4cA8wAM0BigM2DRBtfxAwwA2weHAPMADNAYoDNg0QbX8QMMANsHhwDzAAzQGKAzYNEG1/EDDADbB4cA8wAM0BiQLd5REVFIdy/3o8EDKrKjIMU69IuigQ9KBgMmYc09rliZoAZsJwBo5MDQ+ZhtHLL2ZjVAYq72g0Dzzzsp0gkxBUFA5uH/WJRs0cUoTUrtaAA47CA9ABNUrRg87CPfrp7QhFad+UmFmQcJpKt0RRFCzYP++inuycUoXVXbmJBxmEi2WweoZEtJ1gnMVifgaSS/lmdS4FzoBvFifND67Sfq+XgmMBobwv25e5B27jaaAJynPWoKEhH7PwnhGMwZ+9mCpOjZ1GdfwyL6zukaCEPh9r3XhzdV4yStr8qzUQjpfQg6ndtQmL0k8L1oMQUzzxClkE1DwfOrDqCg6mLQq5NTwUUobXqnRp14eX82yhr34vUaGC8rxbZab/GiKMDnx7PRIwE/5CBYwbOyauoz9iIkv44aUYuzTymhuH6qRP336pBUfIzuCtZD4oWbB5ad5Xm/6p5FOLyS83SRrbZXaAIHRzGFCb6qrH7SwdaMr/vLXoPfWXrkFaXhI7PDiMzep4mE0YLiMcxvQdfKrqUo2loBG1tCD/zGO9EXsNCvHcwFU+psFQzeTkVeWN7MDBcjETBclC0sNA8vsGdzj1YndUMeEe36LtX0FheAOeSRgz7SDMakUHKUwjSbj4SzMMfSt9yLC4MzUOZ8g8eRuHlRFQsP4m4rJHwM4/ZkrjNYz1OprejuzgZohfDlHvDOvOYuALX75/Gq2uu4mdxF7Dpxrt4puc64vJexH/GnsDzK6MheqZMIUifeWxD0xcxuFXXjH73BWtReqIau7YlI1o0CKV2OThmI/XOPK69jpEeB2LDCYd6o+24iOcbC7D04k4sDXvzmMCwqxRFN7NwoibdNjFlnXn4YtXrqC3IRqmrEhtixG8G+ZqSc9OpI3QRziwvQVVmPOZPDqOzughZdUNY29KHHkd8mJjgTPOYutOJHatdeK77Q2U5tlDbQwkl5OihzmirUI3XcSQzBnc73whj8/gao64cZUD9nZddeZumFC2sNw94p8dDb+Kz1kxlT1nej0IQqTcTfSiLT0PdihYpo7Z0HFP/QOeO7fj4hffR7EgQPkWWauYq99l/R16XOlt6gPGwNo/p0ac8Des8gPysWvSvFR9XlJiygXmoG1tbkTTkiBzzeDCI+vgklDwrXmQ1nChC6zdBVY9CNH1vr1TjkINj9kg9C/WzTttsNurXY1pJiZumlJiy2DzUja3f4O2mP+BU73P4cLgGqU9JWFx7+acQFFxk9SnFB2h5egt2T5/au2ceW3GtJtyWLera+i048RoaJc44pM48ZggWrjMPNa7qcEDRYf/0x//uQSkD5wvOCt80pdwbFpmHMgXrH8N3f3QPx5r/jfzCh/jVMhdWDDRj/fVT+POLu5Ab+22SOQe7iEKQVifcewOOIWw5ob4f8SSmxq/iZMO7OPGtIrTbaHNLC4fScVxtrETVw3x0SNjN99e+DD1mtuObifwNpZcuSHsPRwYO93s3KZ9g3dkDynseysMDtz7lyL6WinPN2xAv+MU9CgZrzMM7/apcUos+lYjv3FbW2OuR1bMKzsM7sWVjom12lDVvOqij9W6k5rngfjEzpRQtVXn4eWpsGO0VeJeOJef9w83pkLKkpASsth5qCd+M49jM4uG0bJm6g75KB9JqL3owROfY7t6wxjz0RYDwUvKCVXhXg1bIOMzlW6u1SNCDgoHNQysybPg/RWgbwpC88Wse4kjQg4KBzcO8GBPWEkVoYY0LrIhxCCQzxKooWrB5hEi6FZdThLain1ptMg4thsz7n6IFm4d5+ghriSK0sMYFVsQ4BJIZYlUULdg8QiTdisspQlvRT602GYcWQ+b9T9GCzcM8fYS1RBFaWOMCK2IcAskMsSqKFobMI8T+8eXMADNgYwaMZkcwZB5GK7cbTxR3tRsGtT+Mw16qRIIeFAxsHvaKQ129oQitq2KTCzEOkwkP0hxFCzYP++inuycUoXVXbmJBxmEi2RpNUbRg87CPfrp7QhFad+UmFmQcJpLN5hEa2UKDdXIUfRe60LrzJjYo52X6PSBY+RJysPscOv40iVU/eQXrBH0sZxoOBWPv0X3ILWlzf/QXnXMIrRV5SI91H8kb8k8oDuUDxdG+HnS1NmFow2/R+uggZ/kpDITiCBhXclNjUDDwzMPQLfANxgcvoufM+6j8PAGbb53CoZHtuDTnHBJvvpA3z2NJtXp0vtjzWClCz4SpA4f7NLH1eONBsfvL59ivLqEyOxe1KMFAdxESBXwSHjoO5VDx8UF095xBQ+U/kbz5HuoO/Wvm5/cmpDAIHYe2HrJTY1AwsHkYNo/LuLFgDVJj76Mz9yVkXSmYczqV7PM/KULPNY/gONzBGncEP350DoZ6QE0l4tMuYpugszFCx+E1jxsLkJa6HF/5O3LQhBQGoeNQzSOYHvJTY1AwWGce3in9mYa3UfeDw4/Pi/AeiHx60znhhwdTCArsLcoZJP7MwzdiL5KTPkLtj3wcvkN0gJaRNji8BzN5DCUPY84BDBcnItTUIWJx6Dw1TEIKA7E4AsTVnEAUmxqDgsEy85gabUfl+YVI+q8TWTceH37sCVAlFcO0oDU0ORD8OMqoefhG7ISWciz75B3scacKFJuKgSK0MRwBAlMZxXOXZuFK2JqHnBQG8vXwp57Y1BgUDJaZh4eO2Sene0e80+vC4NRxfyOEb8T+o3Kg2GEcq9qo5HlVUA42IiPpIyTbaLr/OBz94Yg085CbwoBy4xkz87mlRS+NKRhsYR4ZX1R5MsRJXLKYM9333XSLZ0z3lfP/3SN2b+klIZnwKEIbC9ZIM4/p6MWnMJCvxyz1JKTGoGCw2Dw8U69fLD6mrKFX4mv3CN2FV8Iiu7zxETv8zGOmCXqWZPuxpOPytEeh9EUlJWADt6Zzz0OtQHAKA7E4tPY85KTGoGCw2Dw8RJWuOI3hPYvQ5T4EOcPPo096gE6/kkKQsRHb/xMJz033HpZ1nMPxzB+GnEHOGhw+bDdRI2g/SiwOf+ZhTgoDsTiCmYe81BgUDDYxjw9wdvF1tP+lFyfmlQmZ2vu76SkEBTQP3+g1NOs9j8mrqM/YqLwNkY9L7Uo6hgWjcBVuRt4th63ej3iEyyCOynnv4NPjmYgRkF5HqB7wn2bBjBQGQnEE0kNyagwKBovNw7Ns2fr5FrTuXYPbRb/ESNnHNs+v4R0Z2sZm+sq0Y/09uVuqsL1OPTY/ATnOelQUpCubpwLuOGGPavXguILG8gLvEyO74giQZgEpcKrL35X3pacwoNx4cwelYHq8BjQoWRUlpsagYLDYPB5T6HmD7j72C3p7UfrMQ8xKilQLRWhSQ5IvYhySCTZQPUULm5iHZxPoyPL9QvYEAnFGIcgA/6YVZRymUa2roUjQg4LBIvNQvv0YPonC4oeo6NqKBf212P7RCrgEraXZPHTFvOWFKAFreaf9dCAScFAwWGQeytMyNcfr6iy4xpW19KGjOFD0gpQUk/KetlgXxhShrett4JYZh31UoWhhmXlYQRuFICv6qdUm49BiyNz/I0EPCgY2D3PjTEhrFKGFNCy4EsYhmNAQqqNoweYRAuFWXUoR2qq+BmuXcdhHFYoWbB720U93TyhC667cxIKMw0SyNZqiaGHIPOwDlXvCDDADohkwmlpFt3mI7ijXxwwwA+HNAJtHeOvHvWcGLGPg/xyidcJGUAw7AAAAAElFTkSuQmCC\" /></p>\r\n<p>\r\n\tBased on the data, the coefficient a of the linear regression model <img align=\"absmiddle\" alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAEgAAAAiCAYAAAD8gp97AAAETUlEQVRoQ+2Xf0yUdRzHX5hrjpLBsmJUNidwM1ZOqo0tZszIlVkckBgTxkXMChDubO5ai19Ca4fSkYA/8DRIyIKAozE1xbwauSva2R+uNGSsWexsFkYszeFdzz3PcQIC95x3bULP8/f3x+fz+r7f7+/3CXIKH8o3LYEgBdDM6lAAeXGPAkgB5F/AKgpSFKQoyD8CioL846dkkKIgRUHeCYz0YTnaxUfNYWxp1RA1z/uUsRFz3mKjNiNxKTu4JHQcWtiGVRfLfPl8mPOARBajNqof1/G7sY3yhEU+4GE2AhrFbt5MfNcqekxqwuW0azezMe5TnjhmIitqgZwZnjGCgv5x2m3dfN6+h/KmB6myvkdSuEuEV+hryOHZjkQOd/jmW3kVXMVuO8THOw3UdtuFKcE8XNpOm0bFzBHhOyDRZq9A/Ym1DJsb2VbazNnlJWJfSwV4+Yk6jqKmqtsg9P4H39UWkb07gh3WEkFB1844m8q+YumK39ikvUDRGCDHWRqT0zEnH5y6aPFUdHwxHY2wAlp6dcROaXgBjmUbr38SQ12dmghce+VzTndQhgV8BeQev+c2MlYvZ236S0SfeZd4zRDl1rcIO3KSe1OWYc3cIPTaQM1d32CJTibx8gV4JOa6xaQwG/AAcvQ1kPp0N+qbkKVXBYnwxwEZtlD05Ame+rKEhJAp9CNmSCq1Q9OtvIz89ha0sXdOMWAEmzGNtL0qSSER8xm2lBGfi6gQaT+3W5qvkVFgoPj5xR4Ve0JaBJRxie3ipKv/qb1E+EkDFIp7IRVsXEKbLCv7qKAbnOCe/0HshOiYLJBJ17xDKlIXSoPLFld6qV6noWn1gemvxZu2mPu0el6UQlZsIIWahBn2mqALHwG51BlnIrJzLKAvYnk7nfcja8dFh4MRWx3rU/rY6MlgaVO3gtybli0RciOP8C49z2htJDX4fi16tRe/0JnzAuUxJgF+JP0HKnnzw+PcnddKvfp+79PxDdBEtc7DMSiE8nOnSBtv55Feair2c+qzH7hv58SeJwFajEm4yb5vOcmx1hC2eDwqo27ZQ9yAVMXUBJ+nP+EhLmZUMVqSw+WBRRTqViK4LkCf2xma02S370Mb/SuN2u0M5RqFvAphpK+Xn+64h2FTC3/mrIPiDdTHVLNvTT+7v32U4kzVmILcC+UOkl2ziZXnK9Gcy6GnIiGAxY717JJ4KgX2dPZXZPMYh4Tb0ACFel5LX0Ns+O0BgiMt47AfZ+vLBTT9+DfBiZup1mexKsp1BG6rVy6kqMNAlmoBg2aXc6zEjavlxpe0mAmlDJXsEiiHBrTY2bjYJEBSWGXufUB6n/jwUzcbm5dTc5Dzr9PORm0t6I1kLvyara8eYcWud4T3QmClLqeYW3GM8JL+2dmZt543DtsFj+qlXAhwDtyKjcut6f/xNy+XxhTjFEBe4CmAFEB++Ov6r4Z/i8zl2YrFFIv5p+9/Ad3sTk1ncIpgAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC\" /> is estimates as 6.1.<br />\r\n\tThe coefficient b is ________. [Rounded off to one decimal place]</p>",
      "OPT1": "1.9",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "gBhpVqNri9dTS0cBTt0H6w==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "5kxMa8YwwyHwJY15nzG3sQ==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "2",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "Alphanumeric",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu16": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tIn the regression model <img align=\"absmiddle\" alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAaoAAAAjCAYAAADFR05SAAATx0lEQVR4Xu1deVhVx91+NaZP6tZoNEVtkiYqaKxREROjfg0C5jFBDQE1IiAIqChEFlk0Ai7gwiKLgluEsAkFHxDFrQoErbY2bqlLAi6fj7EKiUaN8rmV4Ddzlsu5l3PvPQeugHb48zpzZuad5f0t74ztnpA/sD+GAEOAIcAQYAi0UQTaMaJqozPDusUQYAgwBBgCHAKMqNhCYAgwBBgCDIE2jQAjqjY9PaxzDAGGAEOAIcCIiq0BhgBDgCHAEGjTCDCiatPTwzrHEGAIMAQYAoyo2BpgCDAEGAIMgTaNACOqNj09rHMMAYYAQ4AhwIiKrQGGAEOAIcAQaNMIMKJq09PDOscQYAgwBBgCjKjYGmAIMAQYAgyBNo0AI6o2PT2scwwBhgBDgCHAiIqtAYYAQ4AhwBBo0whoEVV9TRmWL6uGS6or+rdv0/1uYufqUXvhMA7sykNutwDke1hA6TDrL+TAL6cXIpfYwkxpJRW9rK85iT1/P4idW7shZJvHc4q/CkBY0ecWAW6t7ytC5m1H5AVaosNzO1L1A3sWz+CWmM8Goqo9hqQpCcCKDQiwfFk9wm2+Ri1OJk7F1OTvSU8Hwq+ogIyzs4pe3yH15yICQcgPHAE1NQ03Uoea4iCMCSjhi9kl4vAWB5ip6NnzUfQuzh9Iwwr3IGRV0xH9CTPi4rHYZxzMO8tYBnUnED/ACiGXdEbfNw7HK4MxnJ5+tedxYOMKuIdkgX6y14wEZC72wjjzrqoga9eundHyzf9PCGpxIn4irEIqdNqyRtzxEgQP111xSsrrYNprBuIyF8NnnLkJ169RaCQFpHsQeNm/EEfbClHVXkDF/l3IDb8M+/IEfGKmjz61x9AwOOmZchcXyjIR93kCyu+TEh3t4LcuFN62/Q3j/sydwU2bz6bsJ4Go6CHsBY+fP8fhaGuo28ZqFmrrl607mYiRrncQf3QJrLuqc43qrxfDzy4b5jlppifzuxWIGDkTeaPaHlE1ZWGpnen68+n4aM5VhOUugk0voLp8FabbLkWVZyGOfemIPrpTRYlqWCEsj0TDRm4e66+gaNYE+NUFozzVDeb3yhA+3R2rEILjJf4YLkd+ajtt0vKUeDxRYLkeMTY9FHzZWPnHuFYUhBF+DxBdnghP83soD/eE7aoXCfHlEOJrPWOU24OOa4FWJ6rHqDlZir8WbcKamoGwv1aCbVcmY4vBs4Eezj7YPiwJUdZy8/QY14vDMP6Lh1iwPQbu/WtRsWwuvDM7EOPY0Lnx7J7BLTGfHFHVX8iA07gSfGAQSAV7pzWK1BRj9shy2B81ZAWJHRO8l68ssXd7U8JrN1ER7oT5PwdiX6oDeqvjOSOO1UkkjXBCyvC2R1RPf1rrcbc8CoF3PJHm+JrQ3E2Uh42HbawVCq+nwLGXjoVLiWrk1xh7VPCedDrJEZ/Fegwt2ycc/LSNcAyw3Q83zW9Pf2TKW6DE44uvx6bKeE9yXzFSvr4S6R/ZIHxoDipjbHjj8245wgbYItutrOE35R00WUn+YNuC15YWoVBF+N1kHdB8iBLVQVR2eQ/W/e9ih/ckLDjhhoJjgbDUG4+kRBWIQx8kykdk6quQ+akj1gxObTD6BSN0h+NXeh0BQ2dwSxiKzcG2JeaTENWDJxcyvPFRbF+NJSHGHDcs3YM+STux2eEP3Dh4MEvhcGALsRReas7YGtetr8HJnXnY+MVa3l3GaEQoaUcVUfGu6mwsQ9mE/0NxZiKici5isLBhiClEPKZA7IcD1pTGEPf/Fo6nRMBzY2+s5awsstcrlmGMxyUsUNI3NQjV/TcTlb6DmIbCLJpAVA9xPn0GLLyAtKos4k3wa5UnLy9cijuOyuDhCnMjj1F9Yj/2FqyDV+ybkr4IbeSPR9VeT5g322gxLVHxYw0nAJRjr+cAPhcrkJfXpaCG8KiaNWqisvzBlg1Lydki/2lKJHvwl/UxSCmtIUU6avZqs+Fu1OC/TUJU/BkZB0hJWCCvqB+89ZDgQ+iewSaCukU+o3w+6RqsxomSXShIWoLY11NwPdMRJIAirM0JyP9sV8N6lfSeENXVJ5wlgUghN0JAy07Gvn4WeDRvOc4vEYlKAHO7nbw3whFGIMr1QdNtvn5Lpf46cY9DUTBsJVIcXgeZNTh9chn+SsJzqoiKLsYp2NzjY4x7zQ7T5vZHZaQTvGsCydjH4HzGIfzecSCOurmg+NMMrHvln6gw/xR2D34E3hnEiSj4hbgWPWU3mbDYS29rUODj8ENxv4LkSk6NRzbNb4mkxBXrBhv6rQk/CR7VahS4XkSExxZU0a1pF4SkMHfY9OcDstSIKMnbgIjkUvDh7zCkR3vCyuw3JCcjxNm3/gp7l3vYHJSFq668FdfZUD2Dy7kO1UV+6O20iSR5fFF4LAEO7Y8heaEPgrJGy5OISbaH4FF9O0+eCLjQXwJufHgTsQn7+RatQ5ERHwC34V1wisv36JBcdRHcezvhiBqiIod7ZngF+ln9CHenasSK3h136OvfWOohoETlhrU3+uCH2FRUcB/4EKEZUQhwexe9Gp3Mhsv3PBWPAVYbMbrwa2RqvNSrKHIfC6cjPgqIigqPDqGQM+ZOcyRh4boYUX6TYUnXGjUsd+/B9vXfol/Y/+BizFLkfU9WpEw+RnvNmuHPdn/E8dIqjDRIVISkKuIwN38QUmn0guyGzE/9cDEwTybkppPnlQHfeD5MDVHNwsafzXAtp5jbo+RwgHNUOHxdRqDHt3IkbOzbwr9rzmD1q8d4jdaeT76H9edzEb77ZVg9ioPT959riIo3rPbhM4lhKR1Tuyf/OfFENuTEHabe+E4kKs4qcCYHeJ7J3XXu8NcQE++12JSORblsvkxfMrNhWHoXpUAQ6SMThdCdEMojHlZDbk4gZHLYu86PQeTE17WVgQIhn9QbX+djzVOTb8I5o5DfVKJFdUEa/6aLcyb+OiGNI+f2Ink9soN/ZhR8R3THT2SjehHC0pAN5/EtxpUpa5FG1Yf3zyEzwBtR16YjN+wR5nmk4g4HgyWJh38Jb2zFzIOjsfWzHxCgp17BNl9YKsnX1H6D+InTccA+GONudMKECBcM0FdPIIQsvbtHn0CgoUL9tSLMGpGOgSV68imUqBwK8VbCQjiadya6iWJEzfFDbMUY4kWtx5CdU0xDVEKX6k7Qg/+ihqgMbyyBELJ0lR4N4+vbiCwp8fij4K0QRDgOQOfaShRF+cMp9gw+lHpFmk8YLl8yZBfebg5R0fXoehr2uTRETg65k6n4zDEBP9J17/wD5mmMUjPYBCVgud/7ePUnohqeOR85mjwPsZ24eqXEe4pFmIMFOtYcQ25KNJbmXOUNNCFa02ipcHtGQkw0fPbB17A9qD63bPwQpyWMkYn4FXr+hGD7mwHceDrXVmHH6lAsECIz+e/swahG3qKRbxuNppjAWGzt+dSaBEEIdEYkKuPRCSNEFYifE/nD9umF/XhicLroLZAFJQ9nJPdLUUaIKjyqxmPgPayMMRlabfGu7GVEyOW9jBKV6HUtw1WNN0WIN+YYXvn+Nvom5fNeIyGdwFVAWLKQ65JbrFoCi/G4R0O0S7tjjaZfoiV5iw+T9r3Cxce1QwwC8RqqpyiMKyym8Fc5r8qxD7Gqn9YfJ4TwwI7R65Dq+SeFCjUxB5WBwWk7EHUrFO+ZwqOSEtXEW9hcScUbj/nQosnCfnqAFHJKsYPTlIUXJeXPRd3CpPea41GRPlEPvfQcbl/ejSWCB9+gSuWNPO+cIZL1KBqR/fjfXr3Er0ciYJHmhJWEiuSM1zGJJPTapNyykoWqlKhkviXu0/5LUBJ+G25TdMOazSUqoU01xqLckFtxPrW7wxPVxBsRfK5UQXRCP1Fx4MfilRwq467jvYSsMfrDd00N/XGWkweOzNzGWVc8mRQQYYdC+bhioiIHGc0vSRc7N8Yt6LdDmnMTrccLmN1EotJ4UHSDFr6PvzutBuKj8EamC7zPzCSbdhqQFY3d7wQ3qAfliErrNztc18jrdVehKI29IxNnN+SBqpPpc16F5rA2fZaAH9UdTlSwtvsiFSTF1+S9ngT01RBVT5kc1UqYaYXDlBxiAgnO7o4SKn1/SL1LB2y0L1GR61LSjk4ZUYLfVyFRScrzREWxkMlRmUlyA3q6xStcSb72DRdEzPkQo6x/i91jp0rEPjqkxMm5dX7reJhTsu6dpS1DN05UgnF1eDKfjhAiEuuss/XI2Vsy9CcDmLhPXxeJSkcoIkZUeq6Qv3pi1KMS22y6sdi686mLGR/Wn91zE9k/w/DwRDImWu2Evew1DL5uQ47qxnzt3BNHAJvxNiGM+Wal3KI9bEC10oRtyFeRtBNgfgU5q6ORndMT8xSp+MT6SlR/up4bLyOddPwT7RAjucuwLjodp3Z+hz7rhdCddHBcf5cDBuProhfzK/yWDsV3t22QEDgc9ZwQ4yw806bhTvGLmC16U9wpKyOm0PpN9KhgQGQiZ7mJfTFUT8HsUS8nfBV2/OMMzCJ2GJZQNzn0dxeV6ZGII0HLZIOeFFno8dvxOx8vicxc9KguIroqA5P/Ha2j8JP+e4PAQsHI6eTwebrQfiS3Mx9mO4ns2+moAfWg2tAf7dsGpP3OBYFS2TjnIbni22gJ2XAdVlB+8nUs0lX46f2eLgoya6bR+lRAVD1O83lXcoCr86j4dRw1aAshpn64lB2LhVll6OnLG7NP50+JR0WN3c3I7DoNn0vvmnIGry/OhhIVo2M1lhBy1lL4Sf9dVuUotK17BstxYpOMxdaeT92B8PsjdHA+KoN6YCe5RuK0dyLKuGiFvAEsq/rTIpCMCPQ4VYpz+w+hQ5hcIrOZy0YgKvOk+eh4+R4+GHYF7oGPEBHbFZdfdEaA7F2FprQphCpOTEbBtrkwv/YXBIXehs9WmqOhUY5jON/pVdzdUoBfSDgQkS7YPCgJaR9fwsZvhiPSjb5iIXhlClR/GgtGVBD2pgloXroa9a8eDfkrcShy96gkIQW60fsSrDiDYVSDgIJTaB4DrOwtieUpkB20hStiX/TWM+ocUQJJxN4hzhhSMJ2zhL5zvom8C8Phbqr5IWqgb5LDEfHrHBQGv9s43Ccq1hBNwmCu6FQcCs/j9siIHkeEBlSZl4+k4Hy8ELEJ0TZ90J4LkzgQn3YOyujdrC7nke7rjPAOyxruZVEFUnYSgjPMEG/wbpVIVH9EWfGbOJn7N+zO6IoIAxtL7QrlcnKeZ+CSQe+R/YaIo75BdtJyZLzgj1xujNpKRo9Oe4yUp56pK8nT/QeLytIJJl1IuDIQNuG/RYrR0K14sD3g7/4MfcirXxOIgEdzId1Q6K+7YEw9FPK11yV5rH8gNTwIyaV3DSj4BKKyiMS6jldxyfpt3HRdg7ol3nhwuQf8A/9s+ruesnlkOovah7xbp33wm3sOUzeFwJqISuq5nNtq5L0wj88btxdz1HVwzdiASOvOJLURhimxLyGKKonpOdDoT6HqT42xqNVGa8+nPqLagOKe/0Lu6QPI6BBm8MoEf4+Kc/MT8YrUg+AOyUX4cdZyLPjgKha6XlGmwlO7Q8V2fGhCdgRArNUxX5ANsnIupk0ih6/RQ1Rpg7yKiIoTqsi7Dzb+yxEyyxb9OUGAuFC6IIJe0rN4ib+0F3AUI/3D4OP8Ma90gpp7VAaEGlrKSbmwxUQ+xo9dEiUl/S0etvcOYktMpEaua+EaghB3R4y5l8ZdouTFFPRPGtajip8y2XrWgppQHkXxcPwFoYXJJMlvjnruLlIJxiVsxGr/0TJqNKXzIS0nHqq75SvPKMT1r97GXnIvyIsjKiIHv3+WIx6vrLOkTi8i+ItGhNdk2EhenaivPiKoE2mZxi9d8IKIRPyhcBe+dHzDwHNagjfmeg1BmUEYe3UFJlb5mPguEjUGCJF4pXOvaFAFY1oECbfbiK9I6EruHxspT77Bkf9COBD1p9qXObinfKgwgij5OGXp0iE4TMQ0KQ2CVslcCcpVB/ChZ071Kvw2qUMDyVHloPtabJpwGg5EEMStVVk1sLB3apx5RSv2kH0QQy4IS/diU9aZXJ3GSl2ulKZfut7IY1RR4lm6j1PdYiAJjRJVrpO15NUJoojUEDspoqvcleuF7BmsVbB5xmLrzqfuiPnQn2uNCzIXvU9y+QtQFWY4SqPgZQo6UXMRcHueiZ8OMtVCa8HvcKS6juTtnsLLFC04DNYURYA/+K2PTJN/+UIfSJxntwi3Vn7Vqq87sDl83hDQ9zJFSxmLrYMn/yLNL1hp5LUY42/90fenXArw5oYVetzW1hlgy7dKF1IgNnYLRoLHIIVKtJbvJWtRGQI01DYv8h4Ckt30y+wbfYp4piTx67T+DaTLPeukrGlWiiEgj8Az99ZfcyeSF06tf2ulkYgGJ6Z48kRsjn+5938x6t0z+LKdL/JndMEhyUVck0Xhmju+Vqj/tF9Pb4UhsSaVIFBLQ4yJwOJUeHT5G8I9dsMqPfbpyvOV9IuVeS4ReBZfT1c+EcTQq8yGb/CvWLzTFV0qVsFj62BFRp/M/0clPKoYUIz75JY5f/nUTPF/h6G806wkQ+AZQEB43NYp/Sx5fT0Fxatn4V0idmB/DAGGgHoE+Iv8TkivJjljFXlu9h8nqsea1WAIMAQYAgyBFkSAEVULgs2aYggwBBgCDAH1CDCiUo8Zq8EQYAgwBBgCLYgAI6oWBJs1xRBgCDAEGALqEWBEpR4zVoMhwBBgCDAEWhABRlQtCDZriiHAEGAIMATUI/D/O2rVTC2JFssAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" /> denote mean of variables <img align=\"absmiddle\" alt=\"\" src=\"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAAwAAAAMCAYAAABWdVznAAABB0lEQVQoU2P8DwQMJADGQazh37MNDDkuhQy7GAIYevd0MvhLvGM4M6WWIWmGFMOkE/UMDnxMYJ9C/fCG4dCCQwziQZoMJ2KjGTYELmCYLHyS4YBaIIPL95cMDHraDBIQ9TANsGD6wXB7QQqD59K/DDF5nQx1vnIMUHXwcMQIpT/n+hksgu4z1J7oAzqLBSPA0TT8Y/hybipDeNBthjSiNHw5zTC5ZR7D+U3XGKSnrWVodhDBZsPf/19un2a4xS3G8GnOKoaPKaEMDHXRDLO0JzDM9brLMOOUMUNdrDrcL0Anff8P9mgXL0Pt+k6GeHUOhmcbyhk8Ck4wWOSXM2REejEYSbDBbQIAwHN93Ryd3agAAAAASUVORK5CYII=\" /> and y and a is a constant), which of the following values of parameter \u2018<em>b</em>\u2019 of the model is correct?</p>",
      "OPT1": "1.50",
      "OPT2": "1.60",
      "OPT3": "5.50",
      "OPT4": "2.50",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fhPK/WKkcuYMengj9uY6cg==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "7",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.66",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "qu17": {
    "ENGLISH": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "<p>\r\n\tWhich of the following statement is/are correct?</p>",
      "OPT1": "Supervised learning model use labeled data for training.",
      "OPT2": "Unsupervised learning model use labeled data for training.",
      "OPT3": "A supervised learning model gives accurate result.",
      "OPT4": "An unsupervised learning model may be less accurate than supervised learning model.",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fUwGNpwrpUE3GIKhfsyzGA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME"
    },
    "HINDI": {
      "QUESTION_TEXT": "",
      "CORRECT_ANSWER": "fUwGNpwrpUE3GIKhfsyzGA==",
      "SOLUTION": "",
      "ESSAY_ID": "0",
      "EASSY_DETAILS": " ",
      "ESSAY_NAME": "ESSAY_NAME",
      "OPT1": "\u00a0",
      "OPT2": "\u00a0",
      "OPT3": "\u00a0",
      "OPT4": "\u00a0"
    },
    "SUBJECT_ID": "13298796",
    "TOPIC_ID": "18439070",
    "QUESTION_TYPE": "5",
    "LABEL_1": "",
    "LABEL_2": "",
    "ANSWER_TYPE": "",
    "fldUnit": "",
    "IS_IMAGE_TYPE": "0",
    "IS_COMPILER": "0",
    "IS_RECORDER": "0",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE": "",
    "fldTextAreaEnable": "0",
    "SUBJECT_NAME": "Technical",
    "TOPIC_NAME": "Data Science and artificial Intelligence",
    "DIFFCULTY_NAME": "",
    "ESSAY_SORT": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL": "",
    "FREE_SPACE": 0,
    "ESSAY_TIME": "0",
    "MINIMUM_QUE_TIME": "0",
    "isAnswerFileUpload": "0",
    "RIGHT_MARKS": "2.00",
    "WRONG_MARKS": "0.00",
    "MAX_OPT_LIMIT": "0",
    "TIME": "0",
    "ESSAY_SORT_H": "0",
    "SORTING_OPTIONS_H": "",
    "TEST_CASE_TYPE_H": "",
    "OPTION_LABEL_H": ""
  },
  "TEST_NAME": "Discovered Test 6464879",
  "TEST_ID_ENCODED": "NjQ2NDg3OQ==",
  "TEST_ID": "NjQ2NDg3OQ=="
}